(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ダーリンダンス
Darling Dance
作詞・作曲：かいりきベア
Lyrics/Composition: Kairiki Bear
存在証明
Proof of existence
愛だって 愛だって
Even if it's love, even if it's love,
吐いたって
even if I spit it out
嗚呼！
Ah!
ゴロンゴロンてやんやん
Rolling around, yay yay
プリティプリティダイエットで
With a pretty, pretty diet
愛マイ回ラブミー
Love me every ambiguous time
愛マイに愛ラブミー
Ambiguously, love me
病み明かしてんだって
I'm saying I'm staying up all night sick
愛だ恋だなんだってんだ
Love, affection, what's all that?
粘性まー 愛だって
Viscosity, well, even if it's love,
愛だって 嘆いたって
even if it's love, even if I lament
嗚呼！
Ah!
何でもないような
Like nothing at all
寂しい寂しいナウセプティックで
In this lonely, lonely "Now Septic"
一生マイ回ラブミー
Love me every "My" time for life
一生舞い愛ラブミー
Dancing love for life, love me
溺れ取れ 踊れ踊れ 惚れた
Get drowned, dance, dance, I've fallen in love
何もない 何もない 私何もない
I have nothing, nothing, I have nothing
ねぇ
Hey
変われない 変われない 私変われない
I can't change, can't change, I can't change
ねぇ
Hey
分からない 分からない わかる分からない
I don't know, don't know, I know I don't know
ハイ
High
もっともっと愛して隠して
Love me more and more and hide me
んっふん
N-fun
ダッダッダッダッダーリン
Da da da da darling
がりがりがりばり
Gari gari gari bari
だらあいちょーまに
Daraai cho-ma ni
嗚呼、メタメタに
Ah, all messed up
ダッダッダッダッ足りない
Da da da da not enough
のりのりがりばり
Nori nori gari bari
逢いたい衝動に
To the urge to meet you
嗚呼、べたべたに
Ah, all sticky
なななななななな
Na na na na na na na na
曖昧性情が怒り 光
Ambiguous nature is anger, light
なななななななな
Na na na na na na na na
内々順序が
Internal order is...
ダッダッダッダッダーリン
Da da da da darling
ちゅっ
Kiss
ダッダッダッダッダーリン
Da da da da darling
あー あいたって あえたって
Ah, even if I meet, even if I can meet
まあ
Well
ゴロンゴロンてやんやん
Rolling around, yay yay
グイグイダイエットで
With a forceful diet
モテいっぱい デスミー
Lots of popularity, death me
ボロボロ手解きで無理
Falling apart, instruction is impossible
病み明かしてんだって
I'm saying I'm staying up all night sick
承認承認せえっぱい
Approval, approval, to the fullest
だ 何もない 何もない 私何もない
It's... nothing, nothing, I have nothing
ねぇ はしたない はしたない
Hey, it's improper, improper
私 はしたない
I'm so improper
ねぇ 分からない 分からない
Hey, I don't understand, don't understand
分かる分からない
Understanding, not understanding
失態は全部曝して
Expose all the failures
ダダダダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da Darling, Darling, Darling
マイナー愛を飲んで 冷めたら
Drinking minor love, when it cools down
ダダダダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da Darling, Darling, Darling
アテンションそっぽ向いて ダダダダーリン
Ignoring attention, da-da-da Darling
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance
叫べ 叫べ
Shout, shout
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance
ルラッパッパ
Ru-ra-pa-pa
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance
唱え 唱え
Sing out, sing out
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance
ルラッパッパ
Ru-ra-pa-pa
もっとドキドキの
More heart-pounding
シドドきの
A gloomy time
配慮は全部失くして
Lose all consideration
ダダダダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da Darling, Darling, Darling
どうしようもない感情に 今笑ったり
Laughing at these helpless emotions now
ダダダダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da Darling, Darling, Darling
アテンションうめてよ ダダダダーリン
Fill me with attention, da-da-da Darling
意味も無く 感情で ダダダダーリン
Meaninglessly, with emotion, da-da-da Darling
ねぇ ダーリン チュッ
Hey, Darling, mwah
愛して愛して愛して
作詞・作曲 きくお
Love Me, Love Me, Love Me
Lyrics & Composition: Kikuo
ああああああ...
Ahhhhhh...
はるか遠い 遠い昔 撒かれた首輪
A collar put on a long, long time ago
人が欲しい 人が欲しいと 叫ぶ呪いの首輪
A cursed collar that screams, "I want people, I want people!"
怒らないで 見捨てないで どこも行かないで
Don't be angry, don't abandon me, don't go anywhere
強く絞める 吐くまで絞める 人がいない いないと
Tighten it hard, tighten until I vomit, because there's no one here
いい成績でしょう ねえ
Good results, right? Hey
いい子でしょう
I'm a good child, right?
可愛い子でしょう ねえ
I'm a cute child, right? Hey
いい子でしょう
I'm a good child, right?
苦しい ねえ
It hurts, hey
愛して 愛して 愛して
Love me, love me, love me
もっともっと 愛して 愛して
More and more, love me, love me
狂おしいほどに
To the point of madness
苦しい 苦しい
It hurts, it hurts
呪縛を 解いて 解いて
Untie, untie the spell
止められない
I can't stop
ああああああ...
Ahhhhhh...
体 体 大きくなっても 小さい首輪
Even as my body grows bigger and bigger, the collar stays small
苦しくなる 足りなくなる 人が 人が 足りない
It gets painful, it's not enough, people, people aren't enough
クラスの誰にも負けない 綺麗な子でしょう
I'm a beautiful child, second to none in class, right?
あの子よりも どの子よりも 誰もかれも 私を見てよ
More than that child, more than any child, everyone, look at me!
体育館裏 あなたに告白を
Behind the gym, confessing to you
嘘みたいでしょう
It's like a dream, right?
あなたが好きなの 汚いあなたが
I love you, even the dirty you
愛して 愛して 愛して
Love me, love me, love me
全部あげる あなたに あなたに
I'll give everything to you, to you
全部背負ってもらうよ
I'll make you carry it all
足りない あなたが
Not enough, you're not enough
足りない 離さないよ
Not enough, I won't let go
ああああああ...
Ahhhhhh...
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry
愛して 愛して 愛して
Love me, love me, love me
もっともっと 愛して 愛して
More and more, love me, love me
狂おしいほどに
To the point of madness
苦しい 離さない
It hurts, I won't let go
苦しい
It hurts
ねぇ、もっともっともっと
Hey, more, more, more...
幸せなの、お
I'm happy...
はい、ということで
Alright, and so...
ちょっと待ってね
Wait a second...
はい！えー、夏色まつり誕生日ライブ、
Yes! Uh, Natsuiro Matsuri Birthday Live,
夏色ReSTART、開幕しましたー！イエーイ！
Natsuiro ReSTART, has begun! Yay!
えー、ダーリンダンス、愛して愛して愛してを
お聞きいただきました。
Uh, you just listened to 'Darling Dance'
and 'Aishite Aishite Aishite'.
どうだった？どうだった、可愛かったやろ？
How was it? How was it? I was cute, right?
ねー、凄く可愛かったでしょ？
Right? I was really cute, wasn't I?
この日のために、可愛さをムッシュムッシュに
してきました。
For this day, I've brought my cuteness
to the max!
イェーイ、可愛い？ほらほらほらほら
Yay, am I cute? Look, look, look, look!
そして、何とね、あの、もう気づいた方も
いるかもしれないんですけど、
And also, surprisingly, some of you
might have noticed this already,
まつりすも、頭の上にいます。どう？可愛いでしょ。
Matsurisu is also on top of my head. How is it? Cute, right?
誕生日だからね、一番近くで祝ってもらおうかなと
思って、
It's my birthday, so I thought I'd have him
celebrate from the closest possible spot,
特別席、特等席を作りましたよ。
so I made a special seat, a prime seat for him.
何とね、どんぐりも食べれたりするみたい。
どう、やってできる？できますか？
And apparently, he can even eat acorns.
How about it, can you do it? Can you?
そう、これ、めっちゃ可愛くない？
ねえ、可愛いよね、これ。
Right, isn't this super cute?
Hey, it's cute, isn't it?
他にもなんかワチャワチャって、なんか動けるみたいで。
He can also move around all excitedly and stuff.
うん、可愛いでしょ？そう、めっちゃ可愛いんですけど、
Yeah, cute, right? Right, he's super cute, but...
まぁまつりよりはちょっと負けてるかな。
well, I guess he's slightly less cute than Matsuri.
まつりのほうが可愛いみたいなところありますね。はい。
There's a point where Matsuri is cuter. Yes.
そして、そしてですね、ここからは何と、
And, and then, from here on...
豪華ゲストによるコラボパートなんですが、
ちょっと一旦水を飲んでいいですか？
it's the collaboration part with gorgeous guests,
but can I drink some water for a moment?
いいですか、いただきます。はい、すみません。
Is it okay? Thank you. Yes, sorry.
はい、大丈夫です。
Okay, I'm fine.
えー、コラボパートなんですが、
Uh, as for the collaboration part,
ハッシュタグ夏色リスタートでツイートして、
please tweet with the hashtag #夏色ReSTART,
たくさんたくさん盛り上げて欲しいので、
I want you guys to hype things up a lot,
皆さん夏色リスタート、ハッシュタグ付けて
ツイートお願いします。
so everyone, please tweet with
the hashtag #夏色ReSTART.
はい、ということで早速いきたいんですが、
Alright, so I want to get started right away,
楽曲も神ってるので、
the songs are also godly,
最後までコメントたくさんして、
so please comment a lot until the end,
まぁまつりちゃん推しの人がほとんどだと
信じたいんですけど、
well, I want to believe most of you are
Matsuri-chan fans,
まぁ他に推しいる方はね、他の子も全力で
愛してあげてください。
but for those who have other favorites,
please love the other girls with all your might too.
では、早速いきましょう。
Now, let's get started.
コラボパート、スタート！
Collaboration part, start!
にっこり調査隊！おはこんばんわ！
Niccori Survey Team! Good morning, day, and night!
今日も今日とて最高です！わんだほーい！
Today is also the best! Wonderhoy!
しゅっぱーつ！はい！
Departure! Yes!
我々は世界の笑顔を調査する！
We're going to investigate the world's smiles!
はい隊長！俺に名案があります！
Yes, Captain! I have a great idea!
窓の外にも行ってないんだった！
We haven't even gone outside the window yet!
とにかくあれだフレア。
Anyway, it's that, Flare.
ねねぼんはイケメンにしとく？
Should we make Nene-bon a handsome guy?
百聞は一見にしかずだね！
Seeing is believing!
とりあえず一人一匹！
For now, one for each person!
どうして隊長、名案があります！
Why, Captain? I have a great idea!
ぜひ聞かせて欲しいものだなぁ。
I'd really like to hear it.
とりあえず、とりあえず
For now, for now...
出発しようノープランで！
let's depart with no plan!
ちょっと待って！出発進行！
Wait a minute! Full speed ahead!
ちょっと待ってって旅支度ぐらいさせろ！
I said wait a minute, at least let me prepare
for the trip!
数日後…準備もチェックハジケマース！
A few days later... Prep check, let's pop!
まずは基本のパパパパスポート持った？
First, the basics: did you bring your
pa-pa-passport?
はい！着き着き着替え忘れた！
Yes! I forgot my ch-ch-change of clothes!
エモーモバイルバッテリー持った？
Did you bring your e-mo-mobile battery?
はい！心意気は持った！
Yes! I've got the spirit!
もちろん！
Of course!
仲間がいて
With comrades by my side
私がいる
and me here too
ギガが普通じゃない
The giga isn't normal
誰のことかな？
I wonder who you're talking about?
僕らには不可能を可能に変える何かがあるさ！
We have something that turns the impossible
into possible!
どこに？どこに？どこに？あんだ！
Where? Where? Where? There!
あっちもこっちも千客万来！
Customers coming from here and there!
君の笑顔をコレクションにさせて！
Let me add your smile to my collection!
イェーイェーイェーイェー！
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
大人も子供も関係ぜ！
Adults and children don't matter!
これぞ一等の一流のエンターテインメント！
This is first-class entertainment!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I'll fulfill my dream someday too
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れてもっともっと
Touch this smile and more and more...
...胸膨らみましたとさ
...And so their hearts swelled with joy.
おお！
Whoa!
そのしょんぼりをにっこりに変換
Turn that gloom into a smile.
うちらに任せろ Make you smile!
Leave it to us, we'll make you smile!
上げの時だって下げの時だって
When you're up and when you're down.
かき混ぜちゃってスパイスだって
Mix it all up, even the spices.
完璧だ！
Perfect!
ガリガリガリガリ有難ジャン
Gari gari gari gari, thank you-jan!
大人も子供もメンツ歓迎
Adults and children alike are welcome.
もち我々も調査対象だ
Of course, we're also subjects of the survey.
なのべい いえいえいえいえーい
Nanobei, yeah yeah yeah yeah!
いつだっていつか夢を叶えてやるぜ
Always, one day, we'll make our dreams come true.
We can do it!
にっこりに触れてもっと
Experience a smile more and more.
胸膨らみましたとさ
And so their hearts swelled with joy.
あ・い・う・え・おにぎり / 作詞・作曲：しゅうさえこ
A-I-U-E Onigiri / Lyrics & Composition: Shu Saeko
朝から一緒に おにぎり
Onigiri together from the morning.
一日中 笑顔で おにぎり
Onigiri with a smile all day long.
心も 体も
Both heart and body.
ぽっかぽかに なる
Will feel nice and warm.
あ・い・う・え・おにぎり
A-I-U-E Onigiri.
今日のおにぎりの中身は？
What's inside today's onigiri?
梅干しー！
Pickled plum!
梅干し！
決めた！
Decided!
あれあれ いつから おにぎり
Oh my, since when onigiri?
ウキウキ エクボで おにぎり
Onigiri with cheerful dimples.
心も 体も
Both heart and body.
ぽっかぽかに なる
Will feel nice and warm.
あ・い・う・え・おにぎり
A-I-U-E Onigiri.
今日のおにぎりの中身は？
What's inside today's onigiri?
鮭ー！
Salmon!
鮭！
決めた！
Decided!
真っ白 ふっくら ちょっぴり塩味
Pure white, fluffy, and a little salty.
ギュッと 握った その形
That shape squeezed tight.
たまらなーい！
I can't resist it!
朝から一緒に おにぎり
Onigiri together from the morning.
一日中 笑顔で おにぎり
Onigiri with a smile all day long.
心も 体も
Both heart and body.
ぽっかぽかに なる
Will feel nice and warm.
あ・い・う・え・おにぎり
A-I-U-E Onigiri.
今日のおにぎりの中身は？
What's inside today's onigiri?
おかかー！
Bonito flakes!
おかか！
決めた！
Decided!
あ・い・う・え・おにぎり
A-I-U-E Onigiri.
おにぎりー！
Onigiri!
おおー！
Oooh!
神のまにまに / 作詞・作曲：れるりり
At the Mercy of the Gods / Lyrics & Composition: Rerulili
思い通りにいかないことだらけ
Everything is full of things that don't go as planned.
どうしようもなく自己嫌悪
Hopelessly filled with self-hatred.
八百万の痛みや悲しみから
From the countless pains and sorrows,
逃げ込める場所を探してる
Searching for a place to take refuge.
いっそ岩の隙間に引きこもって
I'd rather shut myself in a cave,
月も太陽も無視して眠ろう
And sleep, ignoring both the moon and the sun.
生まれてきたことの意味なんて
The meaning of being born into this world...
知らない 分かんないよ
I don't know, I don't understand.
でもそんな風に思えるってこと
But the fact that you can feel that way,
それは君がもっともっと素敵になれる
It teaches you that you have the power
力があるって教えてるんだよ
To become even more wonderful.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, at the mercy of the gods.
...のまにまに
...as you wish,
仰せのままに
just as you say.
誰かが地球を愛してる
Someone out there loves this world.
飲めや歌えやどんちゃん騒ぎ
Drink, sing, and make a ruckus.
たまにゃそんなのもいいいね
Sometimes, that's not so bad, right?
そうさ北も南も
That's right, from north to south,
右も左も
from right to left,
なんだかんだ地球を愛してる
one way or another, they love this world.
泥んこだけど
It's covered in mud,
歩いていける
but we can keep walking.
まだまだ先は長いさ
The road ahead is still long.
淡々と踊っていたいんです
I just want to dance nonchalantly,
そんな誰もが願っているけど
though that's what everyone wishes for.
八百万の心の醜さに
To the ugliness of millions of hearts,
苦しめられる毎日さ
I'm tormented every single day.
僕が生まれてきたこと
The fact that I was born into this world,
奇跡と言えば聞こえはいいけど
sounds nice if you call it a miracle,
それはきっと偶然に過ぎなくて
but it's surely nothing more than a coincidence,
やっぱり意味なんてないさ
so there's really no meaning at all.
でも例えば君にいじわるをする
But for example, if there's someone
奴がいるなら
who's being mean to you,
それは君がとっても素敵な人だって
it's just a sign that you're a truly wonderful person,
教えてるんだよ
that's what it's telling you.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, as the gods will,
仰せのままに
just as they say.
誰かが地球を愛してる
Someone out there loves this world.
僕が笑って
If I smile,
君も笑えば
and you smile too,
許せないことなんてないよ
there's nothing that can't be forgiven.
そうさ男も女も
That's right, both men and women,
恋しかるべき
should fall in love.
そんなふうに地球は回ってる
That's the way the world keeps spinning.
泥んこだけど
It's covered in mud,
歩いていこう
but let's keep walking.
まだまだ先は長いさ
The road ahead is still long.
本当に大事なものなんて
The things that are truly important
案外くだらないことの中に
can be found within things
あるよ
that seem surprisingly trivial.
時機も見計らって馬鹿騒ぎ
Biding our time for a wild celebration,
裸踊りで
dancing naked,
構わない
I don't mind at all.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, as the gods will,
仰せのままに
just as they say.
もっともっと自分を愛せるよ
You can love yourself more and more.
鏡を見てごらんよ
Just take a look in the mirror.
もう分かるでしょみんなを照らす光さ
You see it now, don't you? You're the light that shines on everyone.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, as the gods will,
みんなありがとう
thank you, everyone.
やっぱり地球を愛してる
After all, I do love this world.
花を咲かそう
Let's make flowers bloom,
大きな花を
big, beautiful flowers,
天まで届くくらいの
high enough to reach the heavens.
Hey DJ カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, let's go, yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の針を落とせ
Drop the needle for the ultimate high!!
音鳴らせパーリナイ
Let the sound ring out, it's party night!
飲もうライライライみんなで踊れ
Let's drink, lai lai lai, everyone dance!
Hip Pop Bee Pop かけてよミラクルナンバー
Hip Pop, Bee Pop, play that miracle number!
喜びのあまり分かち合え
Share the overflow of joy,
探したくて回す地球儀
spinning the globe, wanting to find it.
ぐらつく不安定生活それだからバランス重視
Life is shaky and unstable, so I prioritize balance.
良い事ばかりじゃないから頑張れる最悪な日に聞く
It's not all good things, so I can try hard; I listen on the worst days.
再起動のボタンクリック DJ かけて今を取り戻せ
Click the restart button; DJ, play it and reclaim the moment!
洒落てるビートに乗せ
Ride on this stylish beat,
感じる体揺らせよ
feel it and let your body sway!
Hey DJ カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, let's go, yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の針を落とせ
Drop the needle for the ultimate high!!
音鳴らせパーリナイ
Let the sound ring out, it's party night!
飲もうライライライみんなで踊れ
Let's drink, lai lai lai, everyone dance!
Hip Pop Bee Pop かけてよミラクルナンバー
Hip Pop, Bee Pop, play that miracle number!
Hip Pop a lampin' pumps
Techno House a Hip Pop
オリジナル活かすキーポイントそれぞれの色重ね合わせて
The key point is to use your originality, layering each of our colors.
君に聞かせたい最高の結末を果て
I want you to hear the end of the ultimate conclusion,
十時かさね今を楽しみ痛いんだ
it's ten o'clock, I want to enjoy this moment so much it hurts.
Hip Hop pop till you here we go
乱反射フロアの上
Above the floor of diffused reflections,
頭の中揺さぶる
it shakes inside your head!
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
気分上々↑↑の波に乗って
Riding the wave of high spirits
はじけてファンキー・ナイト
Bursting out on this funky night
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
Hip Pop, Pop, 朝まで be lovin'
Hip Pop, Pop, be lovin' 'til morning
ミラクル・ナンバー
Miracle number
ミラーボール スモーク この匂い
Mirror ball, smoke, and this scent
溶けるようなハーモニー
A harmony that seems to melt
身にまとって踊り明かす
Clad in it, we'll dance the night away
ガムシャラなままで
Just as reckless as can be
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Hey DJ, bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の針を落とせ
Drop the needle on our high spirits
鳴らしてファンキー・ナイト
Let that funky night ring out
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
Hip Pop, Pop, かけてよ
Hip Pop, Pop, play it
ミラクル・ナンバー
Miracle number
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Hey DJ, bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
気分上々↑↑の波に乗って
Riding the wave of high spirits
はじけてファンキー・ナイト
Bursting out on this funky night
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
Hip Pop, Pop, 朝まで be lovin'
Hip Pop, Pop, be lovin' 'til morning
ミラクル・ナンバー
Miracle number
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Hey DJ, bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Hey DJ, bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
No more ライ・ライ・ライ
No more rai-rai-rai
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah!
Hey DJ, bring it on, yeah yeah yeah!
I love music, I love you, I need music...
なんか最近元気なくない？
You're looking a bit down lately, aren't you?
あまり眠れてないみたいだし
You look like you haven't been sleeping much.
友達だし隠し事なし
We're friends, so no secrets between us.
話してごらんよ
Tell me what's on your mind.
だってテレビ見てもネットしてても
I mean, whether I'm watching TV or browsing the net,
つまんないニュースばかり
it's nothing but boring news.
それに宿題だってやらなきゃダメって
And I'm always told I have to do my homework,
詰まっていくばかり
it just keeps piling up.
そんなに 塞ぎこんで
If you're going to shut yourself away,
遠ざけてゆくなら
and push me back like that,
その指で その声で
with those fingers and that voice,
魔法を奏でてみようよ
let's try creating some magic.
誰もの心の中にも眠る不思議な力
There's a mysterious power sleeping inside everyone's heart.
疑わないことでいいじゃない
It's fine not to have any doubts.
当たり前なことでいいじゃない
It's fine for it to be something natural.
君の心の中にも眠る素敵な力
There's a wonderful power sleeping inside your heart too.
それはMUGIC 僕らをつなぐ魔法の言葉
That's MUGIC, a magic word that connects us.
どうしてたの？ こんなに近く
Why has it been like this? We're so close...
手を伸ばせば届く距離なのに
within arm's reach...
焦れったいばかり すれ違ってばかり
it's just frustrating, we keep missing each other.
気づけば顔真っ赤っか
Before I know it, my face is bright red.
恥じらいメールのやり取りじゃなく
It's not about exchanging shy messages,
伝わらないことってあるよね
there are some things that just don't get through.
男の子なら そういうことは
If you're a boy, those things,
はっきり言わなくちゃ
you have to say them clearly.
一人で 抱え込んじゃって
If you keep it all to yourself,
何も変わらないから
nothing is going to change.
君の声と 僕の声で
With your voice and my voice,
奇跡を起こしてみようよ
let's try and make a miracle happen.
誰もの心の中にも眠る不思議な力
There's a mysterious power sleeping inside everyone's heart.
頑張ってみればいいじゃない
It's fine to just give it your best shot.
晴れたら休めばいいじゃない
It's fine to take a break when it's sunny.
君の心の中にも眠る素敵な力
There's a wonderful power sleeping inside your heart too.
それはMUGIC 僕らをつなぐ魔法の絆
That's MUGIC, a magic bond that connects us.
数千年前も数百年前も　ずっとずっとずっと先の未来も
Thousands of years ago, hundreds of years ago, and far into the future,
絶え間なく繰り返されるそれは
it will be repeated endlessly.
言語も国も性別も越えて
Across languages, countries, and genders.
名前も知らない顔も知らない
Without knowing names or faces.
まだ会ったこともない君のところへ届いていくよ
It will reach you, whom I haven't met yet.
このメロディが響いていくよ　この世界に
This melody will resonate throughout this world.
誰の心の中にも　眠る不思議な力
Within everyone's heart, lies a mysterious sleeping power.
君の心の中にも　眠る素敵な力
Within your heart too, lies a wonderful sleeping power.
誰の心の中にも　眠る不思議な力
Within everyone's heart, lies a mysterious sleeping power.
くだらないことでいいじゃない　ありきたりのことでいいじゃない
It's okay to be silly. It's okay to be ordinary.
君の心の中にも　眠る素敵な力
Within your heart too, lies a wonderful sleeping power.
それはミュージック　僕らを繋ぐ魔法の言葉
That is music, the magic word that connects us.
I love music. I love you.
I need music. Ooh...
I need music. I need you.
I love music. I love you.
I need music. Ooh...
I love music.
ファンサ
Fansa
もっともっと私を見て　もっともっと恩返しは
Look at me more and more. My repayment is...
愛のこもった投げキッスで　ハッ！
with a blow kiss full of love. Ha!
気のせいじゃない　目が合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes are meeting.
ハート作って　恋しちゃってください
Make a heart, and please fall in love.
やれること　なんでもします
I'll do anything I can.
NGなしで　体当たり挑戦
I'll give it my all with no NGs.
エゴサで見つけたアンチのコメ
The anti-comments I found through ego-searching.
「ふざけんな」　誰より分かってるし
"Stop joking around." I know that better than anyone.
でも大丈夫　ここに立てば
But it's okay, when I stand here,
みんながいる　（いくよー！）
everyone is here. (Here we go!)
好きになって　もっと私を見て　もっと
Please love me. Look at me more and more.
恩返しは　愛のこもった投げキッスで　ハッ！
My repayment is with a blow kiss full of love. Ha!
虜にする　もっと
I'll captivate you more.
夢を見せる　もっと楽しんでって
I'll show you a dream. Please enjoy yourself more.
愛のこもったスペシャルな愛を
A special love filled with love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
お手紙も書いてください
Please write me letters too.
何度も読んで　宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and make them my treasure.
スキャンダル　まだ早いけど
Scandals are still too early,
裏切りません　宣言しときます
but I won't betray you. I'm declaring it now.
嫉妬嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment.
「ふざけんな」　実力で勝ってやる
"Stop joking around." I'll win with my ability.
だからやめない　負けず嫌い
So I won't quit. I'm a sore loser,
私はいる　（いくよー！）
I am here. (Here we go!)
拳上げて　もっと汗をかいて　もっと
Raise your fists. Sweat more and more.
恩返しは　愛のこもったまつりビームで　ハッ！
My repayment is with a Matsuri-beam full of love. Ha!
大歓声　もっと
With great cheers, more.
まだまだね　もっと受け止めてね
Not yet. Please accept it more.
愛のこもったわがままな愛を
A selfish love filled with love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
終わりが近づく　寂しいね
The end is approaching. It's lonely,
楽しいのに　泣きそうだ
even though it's fun. I feel like crying.
次も次も　また会えるよね
Next time and the time after, we can meet again, right?
約束ー！
Promise!
満たされている言葉も
The words that satisfy me,
心無い誰かの言葉さえも
And even the heartless words of someone else,
必要なんだ
They are necessary.
強くなろう
Let's become stronger.
好きに叫べ もっと
Shout as you like, more!
楽しんじゃえ もっと
Just enjoy it, more!
忘れないで
Don't forget,
特別な日になりますように
May it become a special day.
共に歌おう ずっと
Let's sing together, always.
共に歩もう ずっと
Let's walk together, always.
合言葉は
The password is...
とびっきりのLOVE!
An extraordinary LOVE!
気になって もっと
Get curious, more!
まつりを見て もっと
Look at Matsuri, more!
恩返しは
My repayment is...
愛のこもった投げキッスで
A blow kiss filled with love.
虜にする もっと
I'll captivate you, more!
夢を見せる もっと
I'll show you dreams, more!
楽しんでて
Keep enjoying yourself.
愛のこもったスペシャルな歌
A special song filled with love.
恋しちゃうぞ
I'll make you fall in love!
はーい！ということでコラボパートからの
Hi! So, after the collab part...
まつりちゃんの『ファンサ』までいかがだったでしょうか！？
...to Matsuri-chan's "Fansa", how was it!?
噛んでないよ！いかがだったでしょうか！？
I didn't stutter! How was it!?
いや、めちゃめちゃ可愛かったよね。
Man, it was super cute, right?
みんなもね、あの、いっぱい協力してくれて嬉しかったでございます。
I'm so happy that everyone cooperated so much.
ということで、みんな気づいたことない？
So, hasn't anyone noticed something?
これで気づかないやついたら、ちょっとアレですけども。
If there's anyone who hasn't noticed by now, that's a bit...
どうよ、どうよ！
How about this! How about this!
この可愛い衣装！
This cute outfit!
そして、この素晴らしい、素晴らしいこのステージ！
And this wonderful, wonderful stage!
今回の、えーっと、ために...
For this occasion...
あ、これはですね、100万人をチャンネル登録者数皆様のおかげで行きまして
Oh, this is thanks to all of you for helping me reach 1 million subscribers.
そのね、記念として...
And as a commemoration of that...
まあ、ちょうど誕生日もちょうど良かったんでね、今回お披露目させていただきました！
Well, the timing was just right with my birthday, so I'm unveiling it now!
いや、どうよ、まつりちゃんの欲望まみれの衣装になっております！
So, what do you think? This is Matsuri-chan's greed-filled outfit!
で、ちょっとね、あの、1個ずつ見ていこうかなと思います。
And, I'm thinking of taking a look at it one by one.
まずはお、超絶可愛いお顔からいきましょっか。
First, let's start with this super cute face.
どう？可愛いでしょ？
How is it? Cute, right?
これね、猫耳がこのゲーミング...
This cat ear is, like, gaming...
なんて言うんですか、ゲーミングヘッドフォンみたいな感じになってるんですよ。
What do you call it, it's like gaming headphones.
これ、めちゃめちゃ可愛いでしょ？ロゴもあったりして。
This is super cute, right? It even has a logo.
そしてですね、この、なんとヘッドフォン...
And, this headphone...
ちょっと、とれ、とれる、とれる、んですよ、とれますよ。
Wait, it can be removed! It comes off.
とれますか？とれる、ですか？
Can it be removed? It can?
よいしょ！ほらよ！
Yo-ho! See!
お、ほらほらほら！そうするとね、この...
Oh, look, look! When I do that, this...
ピアス！これホロライブのピアスをね...
Earring! This Hololive earring...
ちょっと作ってもらってつけております！めちゃめちゃ可愛いでしょ、可愛いの。
I had it made and I'm wearing it! It's super cute, right? It is.
そしてそしてね、この、お胸のところいきましょっか。
And then, let's move on to the chest area.
ちょっとセクシーな感じで透け透けなんですけど、これはね、とれませんよ。
It's a bit sexy and see-through, but this won't come off, okay?
ここはとれませんけど、めちゃめちゃ可愛いでしょ。ベルトとかもして。
This won't come off, but it's super cute, right? With a belt and all.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いの。
It's super cute.
そしてスカート！
And the skirt!
これこだわりポイントです。
This is a point of focus.
このちらっと見える、太もも。
This thigh that you can catch a glimpse of.
特に、いいでしょ？
Isn't it especially good?
そしてね、腰もね、めちゃいいんですよ。この肉付きが。
And the waist is also great. The fleshiness.
分かりますか？プニッと感。
Do you get it? The "squishy" feeling.
そう、これね、もしイラスト描いてくれる絵師様がいらっしゃいましたら...
Yes, if there are any artists who would like to draw an illustration...
こだわってほしいですね。そしてね、あの...
I want you to pay attention to that. And then...
足！よくない？この厚底。超可愛くない？
The legs! Aren't they good? These platform shoes. Aren't they super cute?
可愛い、可愛いんですよ。
They're cute, they're really cute.
そして1番こだわったポイント！
And the point I focused on the most!
こちら、ネイルしてるの！
This, I have nails!
これね、まつりがデザインしたんですよ。めちゃめちゃ可愛いでしょ。
Matsuri designed these. They're super cute, right?
超可愛くない？やばみじゃない？これ。
Aren't they super cute? Isn't this crazy?
あれですよ、あの、女性まつりすがいたら、ぜひお揃いにしてください。
You know, if there are any female Matsurisu out there, please get the same ones.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いデザインですよ。
It's a super cute design.
そしてね、ちょっと夏色七変化、七もしないんだけど、しようかなと思います。
And now, I'm thinking of doing a Natsuiro seven-change, though it's not actually seven.
まずは、こちらのヘッドフォン、じゃないわ、猫耳外せるんで、外してくるね！
First, I can remove these headphones... no, cat ears, so I'll go remove them!
ちょっとじゃあカメラさんちょっと向こう見てて、エッチ！
Wait, camera-san, look over there! Lewd!
よいしょ、よいしょ、ほれほれほれほれ。
Yo-ho, yo-ho, look, look, look, look.
どう？どう？また印象違くない？
How is it? How is it? Doesn't it give a different impression again?
可愛いでしょ？可愛いでしょ？エッヘ、エッヘッヘ。
Cute, right? Cute, right? Ehe, ehehe.
そしてそして！まだあるんですよ。
And, and! There's more.
なんと、なんとこのスカートの周りについてるジャケットって言うんですか？なんて言うんだろうこれ。
Actually, this jacket-like thing around the skirt? What should I call this...
スカート隠しみたいなのも、ちょっと脱げるんですよ。
Like a skirt cover or something, it can also come off.
なんとちょっと結構きわどい...
Actually, it's quite risky...
ん～で、時間かかるかもだけど脱いでくるわ。
Well, it might take some time, but I'm going to take this off.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
これ結構ね、ベルトがね、あの、忙しいんですよ。
These belts are quite... a lot of work.
エッチチになるんでね、期待して、
It's going to be sexy, so look forward to it...
コメントたくさん打ってください。よろしくお願いしますよ。
...and leave lots of comments. Please do!
いや、でもさ、この、背景っていうの？この場所もめちゃめちゃ良くない？
But hey, this background? Isn't this place amazing too?
景色いいよね。
The view is great, right?
景色良くて、なんか近未来感もある感じになってて、めちゃめちゃまつりちゃんはスコでございますよ。
It has a great view and a futuristic vibe, I really love it.
はいはいはい、めちゃ綺麗。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so beautiful.
これね、他のホロメンにも使ってほしいと思っているので、
I want other Holo-members to use this as well.
使いたい方はぜひ、ホロメンの中で使いたい方がいたらね、まつりちゃんに言わなくていいんで、スタッフさんに言ってください。
So if any of you Holo-members want to use it, you don't even have to ask me, just tell the staff.
お願いしまーす。
Please!
ということで、お待たせしました！
So, thanks for waiting!
ドドドン！
Ta-da!
え、やばくないこれ？これやばいでしょ！
Whoa, isn't this crazy? This is wild, right?!
めっちゃ、これ斜めなんですよ、実は。スカートがね。
It's actually slanted. The skirt, I mean.
そう、で、太ももが結構見える。
Yeah, and you can see a lot of thigh.
太ももっていうか、もはやお尻なんじゃないかっていう、
Or rather, it's almost at the point where you can see my butt...
ホロライブサマーが帰ってきたレベルのエッチチ、エッチチ加減でございますけども。
...with a level of sexiness as if Hololive Summer has returned.
ま、こんな感じでね、
Anyway, with that said...
超絶可愛いまつりちゃんお見せしたところで、
...now that I've shown you this super-cute Matsuri-chan...
そろそろね、ラストスパートに行ってみようかと思います。
...I think it's about time we headed into the final stretch.
スクショも欠かさずしてください。
Make sure to take plenty of screenshots.
そして、あの、Twitterもね、ツイートたくさんしてくれると嬉しいので、ツイートもたくさんよろしくお願いします。
And I'd be happy if you'd tweet about it a lot, so please keep those tweets coming!
ではでは、ラストスパート行きますよ。
Well then, let's head into the final stretch!
では、続いての曲、かっこいい曲いっちゃいます。
Now for the next song... It's a cool one!
聞いてください。
Please listen:
ラブカ？
Love Ka?
暗い 暗い 深海路に包まれるわ
Enveloped in the dark, dark deep sea paths.
ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
La la la Love Ka
奪い 奪い 叶わぬ願いは 打ち明けられ
Stealing, stealing, unfulfilled wishes are revealed.
サ サ サ サルカ
Sa sa sa Saru Ka
届け 届け それでも光は 潰え 水面 その遥かラブカ
Reach out, reach out. Even so, the light fades far above the surface... Love Ka?
暗い 暗い 未開の想いは 足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬはラブカ
Dark, dark, unexplored feelings. Insufficient, insufficient, what's lacking is... Love Ka?
ラブカ ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
Love Ka? La la la Love Ka.
ラブなのか？
Is it love?
甘いラビュラビュラビュラブカ それはバブバブバブバブカ
Sweet lovey-lovey-lovey Love Ka? That's baby-baby-baby-baby Ka?
嘘と嘘で濁った 相合二重か？
Muddied with lies and lies, is it mutual love?
去るアイアイアイアイカ 吐息 掃き 掃き出したか？
Leaving love-love-love-love Ka, did you sweep out your sighs?
届かぬ距離で待っていた 意匠か 舞い
Waiting at an unreachable distance, is it a design? A dance?
吐くは病 ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
Breathing is a sickness, la la la Love Ka.
暗い 暗い 深海路に包まれるわ
Enveloped in the dark, dark deep sea paths.
ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
La la la Love Ka
奪い 奪い 叶わぬ願いは 打ち明けられ
Stealing, stealing, unfulfilled wishes are revealed.
サ サ サ サルカ
Sa sa sa Saru Ka
届け 届け それでも光は 潰え 水面 その遥かラブカ
Reach out, reach out. Even so, the light fades far above the surface... Love Ka?
暗い 暗い 未開の想いは 足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬはラブカ
Dark, dark, unexplored feelings. Insufficient, insufficient, what's lacking is... Love Ka?
ラブカ ラ ラ ラ ラブカ ラブなのか？
Love Ka? La la la Love Ka. Is it love?
甘いラビュラビュラビュラブカ それはバブバブバブバブカ
Sweet lovey-lovey-lovey Love Ka? That's baby-baby-baby-baby Ka?
嘘と嘘で濁った 相合二重か？
Muddied with lies and lies, is it mutual love?
去るアイアイアイアイカ 吐息 掃き 掃き出したか？
Leaving love-love-love-love Ka, did you sweep out your sighs?
届かぬ距離で待っていた 意匠か 舞い
Waiting at an unreachable distance, is it a design? A dance?
甘いラビュラビュラビュラブカ
Sweet lovey-lovey-lovey Love Ka.
それはバブバブバブバブカ
That's baby-baby-baby-baby Ka.
去るラビュラビュラビュラブカ
Leaving lovey-lovey-lovey Love Ka.
手に血に落ちていた
Blood was falling on my hands.
届く距離で出会って 闇ならなやめな
Meet within reach, and if it's darkness, just give up.
吐くは病 ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
Breathing is a sickness, la la la Love Ka.
ラ ラ ラ ラブカ
La la la Love Ka
ラブなのか？
Is it love?
知らないくせに
Even though you don't know,
わかったような
acting like you understand,
笑顔見せないで
don't show me that smile.
ホントノワタシ
The Real Me
近くにいても
Even if we're close,
ずっと一緒でも
even if we're always together,
理解もせずに
without understanding,
内心うざがって
feeling annoyed deep down.
今日も無難に
Trying to be likeable today too,
好かれるように
trying to play it safe,
気づけばこんな
before I knew it,
嫌な奴になってた
I'd become such a nasty person.
本当のあたしを
I wonder if there's someone
愛してくれる
who will love the real me...
人はいるのかな
I wonder if they're out there.
ごめんいい子じゃなくて
Sorry for not being a good girl,
ズルくて騙して
for being cunning and deceiving,
壊して期待に
for breaking things and failing
応えられなくて
to live up to expectations.
ごめんできそこないで
Sorry for being a failure,
弱くてダサくて
for being weak and uncool,
腐ってモラル
for being rotten and failing
守れなくて
to keep my morals.
それでも優しいのは
So why are you still kind to me?
なんで
Why?
家族と言えど
Even with family,
異なる命
we are different lives,
きっと全部は
surely we can't understand
分かり合えないよ
each other completely.
嘘つき私
The lying me,
演じる私
the acting me,
誰が見たって
no matter who looks,
嫌な奴で最低だ
I'm a nasty person, the worst.
本当の私を
If you knew the real me,
知ったらきっと
surely I wonder
捨てられちゃうかな
if you'd leave me behind.
ごめんいい子じゃなくて
Sorry for not being a good girl,
妬んで当たって
for being jealous and lashing out,
壊して私で
for breaking things and
悩ませてしまって
making you worry about me.
ごめんできそこないで
Sorry for being a failure,
強がって粋がって
for acting tough and pretentious,
もらった誇りを
for tainting the pride
汚してしまって
I was given.
それでも優しいのは
So why are you still kind to me?
なんで
Why?
胸張れること
There's nothing
今はまだない
to be proud of yet,
けれどもできたら
but if I can,
喜んでくれるかな
I wonder if you'll be happy.
まつりす！
Matsurisu!
いつも本当に応援ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for always supporting me!
まだまだダメダメで、心配ばっかりかけるかもしれないけど、
I'm still no good, and I might cause you nothing but worry, but
これからもずっとずっと一緒に歩いていってください。
please keep walking with me from now on, forever and ever.
大好きだよ！
I love you!
ごめん可愛くなくて
Sorry for not being cute,
見た目も性格も
my looks and my personality,
嫌いで鏡も
hating them so much
見たくないくらい
I don't even want to look in the mirror.
私に構わないで
Don't bother with me,
離して放っておいて
let go and leave me alone,
ぶつけた言っては
even the words
ダメな言葉も
I shouldn't have said that I threw at you.
それでも温かいのは
Even so, why is it so warm?
ごめんいい子じゃなくて
Sorry for not being a good girl,
ズルくて騙して
for being cunning and deceiving,
壊して期待に
for breaking things and failing
応えられなくて
to live up to expectations.
ごめんできそこないで
Sorry for being a failure,
弱くてダサくて
for being weak and uncool,
腐ってモラル
for being rotten and failing
守れなくて
to keep my morals.
それでも優しいのは
So why are you still kind to me?
なんで
Why?
...繋いでくれる
...connecting us.
とても大きな　愛がありました
There was a very great love.
頑張って！追いかけて　ほらもう少しだ　君と加速したなら
Do your best! Chase it! It's just a bit more if I accelerate with you.
もっとギュッと夢を抱きしめに行こう　せーのっ！
Let's go embrace our dreams even tighter. Ready, set, go!
Yes どんなときも　Chance 諦めない
Yes, no matter when. Chance, I won't give up.
夏色のココロが燃えてる
My summer-colored heart is burning.
アイアムミラクルオマツリガール！
I am Miracle Omatsuri Girl!
誇らしい自分になれるように
So I can become a self I can be proud of.
なにクソ　負けるか　すり減った靴底に明日が光るから
Damn it, I won't lose! Tomorrow shines on my worn-out soles.
頑張って！追いかけて
Do your best! Chase it!
もうちょっとなんだ　掴みたいトキメキ
Just a little more. The excitement I want to grasp.
勝手だって言われても　これが私のポリシー
Even if they call me selfish, this is my policy.
だけどご褒美は君の笑顔さ　いつもそばにいてよね
But my reward is your smile. Always be by my side, okay?
それだけで元気いっぱい　ついてきてよ後悔させないぜ
That alone fills me with energy. Follow me, I won't let you regret it!
ネバギバファイッ！
Never Give Up, Fight!
君もそうだねオマツリチーム
You're part of the Omatsuri Team too.
限界も軽々飛び越える
Leaping over limits with ease.
落ち葉に埋もれた嵐の日
Stormy days buried in fallen leaves.
夢だけは信じて越えてた
I overcame them by believing only in my dreams.
頑張って！追いかけて　辿り着きたい憧れのステージ
Do your best! Chase it! The dream stage I want to reach.
ココロが跳ね出して止まる　抑えきれないよ
My heart starts leaping and then stops. I can't hold it back.
そしてご褒美は君の笑顔さ　そのために前を向こう
And my reward is your smile. For that, I'll look forward.
どんなに深い森も　真っ直ぐ行きゃそのうち抜けられる
No matter how deep the forest, you'll get through if you go straight.
絶望？希望に変えてみます
Despair? I'll try to turn it into hope.
夢の？また夢が見たいから
Is it a dream? Because I want to see a dream again.
負けない気持ちと常夏のスマイルで駆け抜けて
Dash through with an unyielding spirit and an everlasting summer smile.
格好悪くても泥臭くても
Even if it looks bad or unrefined.
叶えるまで走り続けよう
Let's keep running until it comes true.
頑張って！頑張って！
Do your best! Do your best!
追いかけて　ほらもう少しだ　君と加速したなら
Chase it! It's just a bit more if I accelerate with you.
もっとギュッと夢を抱きしめに　行こうよ彼方へ
Let's go embrace our dreams even tighter, to the far distance.
キラキラご褒美は君の笑顔さ　いつもそばにいてよね
My sparkling reward is your smile. Always be by my side, okay?
それだけで元気いっぱい　ついてきてよ後悔させないぜ
That alone fills me with energy. Follow me, I won't let you regret it!
ネバギバファイッ！
Never Give Up, Fight!
はい、まだ帰らないで！
Wait, don't leave yet!
ライブを最後まで見てくれたそこの君、本当にありがとう！
To those of you who watched the live until the end, thank you so much!
今からは告知タイム！
Now, it's announcement time!
では、行きます。誕生日記念2022ということで
Okay, here we go. It's the Birthday Anniversary 2022...
えー、今回もありますよ、フルセット
...and we have it again this time, the full set.
記念グッズが4種類
There are four types of anniversary goods.
B2タペストリー、ライブロゴタオル、ラバーバンド、キーホルダー
B2 tapestry, live logo towel, rubber band, and key holder.
ということでね、フルセットの数量限定バージョンもあって
There's also a limited quantity version of the full set.
なんとそちらには、直筆サイン入りのチェキ風ブロマイドカードも付いてくるということでね
And surprisingly, that one comes with a hand-signed Instax-style bromide card.
お願いします。売り切れてください、と、あのー、願うばかりでございます
Please. I just hope, well, I just hope it sells out.
はい、そしてですね、まあ、この画像にもなっている
Yes, and then, well, it's also in this image...
まず、グッズから見ていこうかなと思います
...I think I'll start by taking a look at the goods.
まず一つ目、こちら。ドドン！
First one, this one. Ta-da!
B2タペストリー
イラスト：皆村春樹
B2 Tapestry
Illustration: Haruki Minamura
パッパッ！描き下ろしてくださった、え、タペストリーでございます！
Pappa! Here is the newly drawn, uh, tapestry!
バーカ可愛いクマい、めっちゃ可愛いでしょ。
It's so crazy cute, right? Super cute.
はい、こちらはですね、えー普段のまつりちゃん、チアアイドル、チアアイドル？チア部のまつりちゃん、
So, this one is... everyday Matsuri-chan, cheer idol... cheer idol? Cheer club Matsuri-chan,
そして、えーみんなの前に立つステージでのまつりちゃん。
and then, Matsuri-chan on stage standing before everyone.
えーそして普段は見せない裏のダンスレッスンで怒られたのかな、泣いちゃう、でも頑張る、そんなまつりちゃん。
And then, me behind the scenes during dance practice—maybe I got scolded? Crying but still doing my best, that Matsuri-chan.
んで、配信でよく見るゲームしてるまつりちゃん。
And Matsuri-chan playing games, which you often see on stream.
そしてそして！真ん中には、今回お披露目した新しい3D衣装でのまつりちゃん！
And then, and then! In the center is me in the new 3D outfit I revealed this time!
はい、今回はですね、リスタートということで心機一転、えー新しい気持ちで頑張るぞというライブになっておりますので、
Yes, since this live is about "Re:START" and making a fresh start with new feelings,
そんな色んなまつりちゃんをね、あの、見ていただけたら嬉しいなと思って、このデザインにしました。
I chose this design because I wanted you all to see all these different sides of me.
ライブロゴタオル
ロゴデザイン：柊
Live Logo Towel
Logo Design: Hiiragi
続いてこちら！はい、ライブロゴデザインのタオルでございます！
Next is this! Yes, it's the live logo design towel!
らぎちゃん、あ、柊先生ですね、がデザインしてくれました。
Ragi-chan... ah, Hiiragi-sensei, designed it for me.
リスタートめっちゃかっこいいでしょ。
The "Re:START" logo is super cool, right?
まつりちゃんがこういうグッズ出すの結構レアでしてね、
It's actually pretty rare for me to release goods like this.
あの、まあ、オタバレしない、友達が遊びに来て洗面所にこれがかかっていても、
It won't out you as an otaku. Even if a friend visits and sees this in the washroom,
「あ、なんかかっこいいライブのタオルかな」って思われるそんなね、かっちょいいライブタオルです。
they'll just think, "Oh, it's a cool live towel." It's a stylish live towel like that.
これ、めちゃおすすめです。
I highly recommend it.
ラバーバンド（2個入り）
Rubber Band (Set of 2)
はい、続いて、はい、バンドでございますね、ラバーバンド！
Next up, yes, the bands! Rubber bands!
これまたおしゃれ。まあ、これはもうオタバレしません。
This is stylish too. Well, this definitely won't out you.
まあ、バレたい人はね、まつりちゃんのキーホルダーも一緒に色々付けていただきたいんですけど、
Well, if you want to be outed, I'd like you to attach my key holders and stuff too,
まあ、これもね、おしゃれでライブといえばこういうバンド付けて、「イエーイ」って感じで盛り上がっていただけたらなと思うので、
but these are stylish too, and for a live, I hope you'll wear these bands and get hyped up with a "Yeah!" feeling.
こちらを買って今日のライブ思い出してください。
Please buy these and remember today's live.
キーホルダー
Key Holder
そして最後に、ドドーン！はい、こちらキーホルダーでございます！
And finally, ta-da! Yes, here is the key holder!
今回はね、全体的に、なんて言うんだろ、まつりちゃんをドンって載せるのは、まあ推してみるタペストリーだけで、
This time, overall, how should I say... having me prominently featured is just for the display tapestry.
あと外に持っていけるようなものは、あの、ちょっと見る人が見たら分かる、って感じのデザインで、
The things you can take outside have a design where those who know will understand.
これ、めっちゃ可愛いでしょ。まつり、めちゃお気に入り、今回のグッズ全部ね。まあ、いつもなんだけど。
This is super cute, isn't it? I really love all the goods this time. Well, I always do.
誕生日記念2022
記念グッズ4種
Birthday Celebration 2022
4 Commemorative Items
はい、ということで、まあそんなちょっと、あの、方向性を変えてみたおしゃれなグッズ、ぜひ手に取ってみてください！
So, please do check out these stylish goods with a slightly different direction!
ということで、改めて本当に最後までありがとう！
With that, thank you so much again for staying until the end!
絶対に買ってくれよな！では、また！おまつりわっしょい！
Make sure you buy them! See you later! Omatsuri-wasshoi!
大好きだぞ。
I love you guys.